Do you want subtitles for any video?
-=[ ai.OpenSubtitles.com ]=-
(dramatic orchestral music)
(thunder rumbling)
- [Man] Hey. hey.
hey. It's me. it's me.
Hi.
We gotta go.
(woman grunts) Okay.
(woman coughing)
(tense music)
(man and woman panting)
(underbrush crunching)
(woman coughing)
(drone buzzing)
(woman grunts)
Come on. hey. hey.
hey. hey. hey.
We gotta go. come on. Come on.
Come on. come on.
get up. get up.
Just get up. just get -
- [Woman] No!
(arrow thuds)
(tense music)
(man panting)
(arrow thuds)
(body thuds)
(birds chirping)
(drone buzzing)
(arrow thwacks)
- [Man 1] A pandemic has
been officially declared
as the as yet unknown
virus sweeps the nation.
The Eradication
Control Task Force...
- [News Reporter 1] Cities
have been left to formulate
their own strategies to deal
with uncontrolled
rates of infection.
Meanwhile...
- [News Reporter 2] Miles
as people flee Chicago
for the countryside...
- [Man 2] That's what
I've been telling you.
There's no feasible
containment strategy.
Absolutely none.
- [News Reporter
3] Record numbers.
and riots are reported
across the nation.
- [News Reporter 4] Comes
days after the release
of viral footage
showing what appears
to be a group of
infected civilians
attacking a military patrol.
- [Woman] There's something
really wrong with people.
We need to get out of here.
- [Man 1] Military
drones have been deployed
across the country in accordance
with the new Eradication Act.
- [Woman] They're not
letting anyone leave.
If anyone leaves their home.
the drones are killing them.
- [Woman 2] It doesn't matter.
We have to go now.
- [Woman 3] Please. you
have to let us out of here.
- [Man 3] Servers are down.
Communications are going
down across the board.
- [Woman 4] They don't
come out in daylight.
but it's getting dark.
- [Man 3] There's no
easy way to say this.
- [Woman 2] If anyone can
hear this. please help us.
- [Man 2] This is an S.O.S.
- [Man] But this will
be our final broadcast.
(drone whooshing) (tense music)
(computer beeping)
- Hey. can you see me?
- Yes. I can see
you. Can you see me?
- Yeah. I can see you.
Yeah. it's working.
- Yay.
- Hi. - How are you?
Did you get back okay?
- Mm-hm.
Yeah. Yes. settled back.
How about you? How is it?
- It's great.
I mean. it's beautiful.
It's very different.
Just being here by
myself. but yeah.
really looking forward
to having you up here.
- Well. actually.
it's going to take
a little longer than we thought.
- Do you know how much longer?
- Well. we're
going to have to do
a lot more testing to figure
out a treatment. so...
As long as it takes. (chuckles)
Did you find the phlebotomy
equipment. by the way?
- Yeah. yeah. yeah.
I got it.
Not great with needles
but I've got these track
marks to make a junkie proud.
Glad that no one
can see me out here.
- You'll be fine.
- How you doing? You okay?
- Yeah. yeah. I'm fine.
Just...
Yeah. I'm fine.
(Sam coughs)
- I actually have to go.
- Okay.
- Yeah. my boss needs me.
- All right.
See you soon.
- Yeah.
- I love you.
- I love you. too.
(computer beeps)
(egg timer ringing)
(David gasps)
(David grunts)
(egg timers ticking)
(tense music)
- [Sam] Dear David...
(egg timer ringing)
By now. you should
be settled in.
I hope you're comfortable
because we need you
to stay isolated.
(egg timers ticking)
(egg timer ringing)
You'll need to keep a
strict daily schedule.
Keep yourself healthy.
Check yourself every
day for symptoms.
(tense music)
(egg timer ringing)
(ax thuds) (wood cracks)
The virus you're infected with
has killed every other person
who's come into contact with it.
Everyone except you.
(tense music)
I'll be at the Eradication
Control Center in D.C.
My job is to study your blood.
It could be the key
to saving us all.
(tense music)
It's a mess out there. David.
and it's getting worse.
Stay isolated.
(tense music) (birds chirping)
(drone buzzing)
(drone buzzes in the
distance) (tense music)
(liquid spraying)
(tense music)
(egg timers ticking)
It's hard to be so
far away from you.
but right now we
don't have a choice.
(egg timer ringing)
(generator starts up)
I'll call every day.
(insects buzzing)
(soft tense music)
One last thing. David...
Never. ever go out after dark.
(insects buzzing)
(tense dramatic music)
I miss you.
(tense music) (insects buzzing)
(guttural screaming
in the distance)
(egg timers ticking)
- It's so funny. I had
this dream that. um...
Oh. I dunno.
It's hard to. to...
(David sighs)
(egg timers ticking)
(dial clicking)
(busy signal beeping)
(phone line trilling)
- [Man] Hello. you've
reached the Beaumont family.
This is Tim-
- [Woman] And Julie.
- [Girl] And Stephanie.
- [Tim] Leave us a message
and we'll call you right back.
(line beeps)
(egg timer ringing)
(drone buzzing)
(egg timers ticking)
(egg timer ringing)
(generator starts up)
(phone ringing)
- Hello?
- [Man] Who is this?
(tense music)
Hello?
(egg timer ringing)
(line drops) - Hello?
Fuck.
(computer beeping)
Shit.
(egg time ringing)
(computer beeping)
No. no. no. no. no. no. no. no.
No.
(David sighs)
(tense music)
(egg timer ringing)
(woman sobbing)
Sam?
(computer beeps)
(David panting)
(egg timer ringing)
(egg timers ticking)
(birds chirping)
(underbrush crunching)
(drone buzzing overhead)
- I'm a vegetarian!
Wha...
(drone buzzing)
(cans thudding)
Okay.
Fine.
Lovely.
(ax thuds) (wood cracks)
(drone buzzing) (birds chirping)
"Virus is a
bloodborne pathogen."
Uh huh.
"Drones are for
your protection."
(egg timer ringing)
(computer beeping)
- [Sam] What are you doing?
- Sam.
- This isn't a game. David.
Do you understand that?
- Yeah.
- There cannot be
any interruption.
It's. it's really dangerous.
Do you understand. your blood
is our only hope for a cure.
- Sam. are you in trouble?
- You have to make the drop.
- Okay.
- Yeah. - Fill another bag.
- I already did one today.
- I need you to do
one right now. David.
David. if they don't
get it within 48 hours-
- Yeah. okay. okay.
I'll do it. just
stay on the line.
Stay on...
(vials clatter)
Yeah.
(tense music)
Sam. I trust you.
You can talk to me.
What's going on?
(Sam sighs)
- The rules are
there to protect you.
Stick to the routine.
Don't take any risks.
Stay isolated.
(computer beeps)
(phone dial clicking)
(phone line trilling)
- [Man] Hello?
- Who is this?
- [Man] Who are you?
- Beaumont?
Is this Beaumont
in Meadow Lakes?
- [Man] No.
How did you get this number?
- Are you in Meadow Lakes?
- [Man] Yeah. what's left of it.
I thought I was only one
here... Where'd you come from?
- [Man] Atlanta.
Nothing there. either.
Look. it's getting dark.
It's not safe for us to talk.
They could hear me... Just you?
- [Man] Yeah. Just me now.
What's your name?
- David.
- [Man] David.
I'm Todd.
- How'd you end up here?
- [Todd] I was in Atlanta
when they lost control
of the infection.
Government drones
appeared out of the sky
and people were cheering.
calling for help.
thought that they
were there to save us.
Then the gas. hissin'.
like timber rattlers.
I had a rebreather on.
working insulation.
Most weren't that lucky.
You know. even before
then you could see
things were getting worse.
People were losing everything.
but I. I always had
the same thought:
to hell with them. it's
not gonna happen to me.
Then along comes
this higher power.
Do you realize you're nothin'?
(Todd scoffs)
I'm ramblin'. I'm
ramblin' at it.
It's been a while since
I had anything to eat.
Look. David...
I know you don't know me.
You've got no reason to
trust me. but I could work.
Earn my keep... You
can't come here.
- I didn't mean that-
- No. you can't be close to me.
I'm infected.
It doesn't affect me. but
um. it would kill you.
so you can't come here.
I'm sorry.
- [Todd] You tested to be sure?
- What?
- [Todd] How long you
been isolated up there?
- 24 months.
- Eradication control
people put out
at home tests towards the end.
I mean. they were
in every drug store.
Didn't help much at that point.
but you could find out for sure.
(tense music)
(insects buzzing)
(birds chirping)
(device clicks) (David grunts)
(blood drips)
(wind chimes ringing
in the distance)
(water sloshing)
(man coughing)
(David panting)
- Stay back.
(man coughs) Stay back.
Hey.
Hey. stay back!
Stay back. I'm infected.
(man coughs)
(tongue clicking)
(man screams)
(water splashes)
(arrow thuds)
(tense dramatic music)
(water splashing)
(David grunting)
(tense dramatic music)
(sick man grunts)
(arrow thuds) (body thuds)
(tense dramatic music)
(water splashing)
(tense dramatic
music) (David panting)
(David panting)
(door thuds)
(match lights)
(David panting) (tense music)
Oh. fucking stupid.
So fucking stupid.
Oh. so fucking stupid.
Oh. fuck.
(David mumbling)
(David breathes heavily)
It's okay. it's okay.
(David mumbles) (tense music)
(birds chirping)
(drone buzzing in the distance)
(tense music) (egg
timers ticking)
- I know this is hard.
but you still have to
keep to the routine.
(David panting) (tense music)
(egg timer ringing)
(egg timers ringing)
Hi.
(ax thudding) (wood cracking)
You'll do fine.
(ax thuds) (wood cracks)
(drone buzzing in the distance)
(woods thuds)
(egg timer ringing)
Actually...
It's going to take a little
longer than we thought.
I'll see you soon.
(egg timers ringing)
David?
I love you.
(egg timers ticking)
(tense music)
(Sam sighs)
Would you look at that view?
I always loved this
place in the summer.
- Yeah.
(Sam humming)
- [Sam] Hey. have you seen.
have you seen the sugar?
- You're not real.
(egg timer ringing)
- [Sam] Turn it off.
- Shut up. shut up. go away.
(Sam chuckles)
- Or what?
It's not like you can make me.
Like you could ever
stand up to me.
(Sam sighs)
I know that look.
That desperate look in your eye.
every time you'd come to me.
Not for support or validation.
you'd come to me so
that I'd lie to you
to tell you it's all
right. you're good.
Your failures aren't your fault.
Your success is right
around the corner.
But nothing I or
anyone else could say
will change the simple
truth that you are a coward.
You have spent your entire
life waiting for permission.
permission to eat.
permission to breathe.
permission to fuck.
Without me to tell you what
to do. you are nothing.
Now turn it off.
- Shut up!
(items clattering)
(egg timer ringing)
(soft piano music)
(egg timers ticking)
(ax thuds) (David grunts)
(David panting)
(David grunts)
(birds chirping) (tense music)
(David laughing)
Oh. fuck.
- Oh God.
I told you not to be
out after sundown.
You can't leave the house
anymore. David. It's not safe.
- The man I saw. there was
something wrong with him.
like he lost his mind.
- Did he bite you?
This is important. David.
Did he bite you or
touch you in any way?
- No.
(Sam sighs)
- That's good.
- What does this
disease do to people?
- I...
I can't say anything
else right now.
but we're gonna clean this up.
Look. I'm not supposed
to say anything.
but we made a breakthrough.
We're close. David. to
finding a cure for you.
A vaccine.
Just a little bit longer and
we can be together again.
I want that so much.
Don't you?
- Sam. you're sure I'm infected?
- Promise me you won't leave
the house again. David.
- Yeah. Of course.
(drone buzzing in the distance)
(soft tense music)
(drone buzzes in the
distance) (soft tense music)
(soft tense music)
(birds chirping)
(drone buzzing)
(soft tense music)
(birds chirping)
(tense music)
(tense dramatic music)
(flies buzzing) (birds chirping)
(flies buzzing)
(David panting)
(birds chirping)
(drone buzzes overhead)
(tense dramatic music)
(birds chirping)
(tense dramatic music continues)
(Sam gasps)
- Sam? - No!
No!
- What is this? What
are you doing here?
- Stay away. stay back.
- Hey.
Hey. it's okay.
I'm not infected.
- I am.
(insects buzzing
in the distance)
Don't. Don't come near me.
(Sam sighs)
- Why did you lie to me?
- I had to.
To protect you.
- I don't understand.
- I know.
I knew you wouldn't.
That's why I had to do it.
- Then help me.
- I can't
- Please.
(Sam sighs)
(Sam sniffles)
- I've missed you so much.
- It's okay.
It's okay. you're here now.
- I made a deal with
dangerous people. David.
They're...
They're killing
everybody who's infected.
- [David] The
Eradication Program?
- Yes.
- There's no cure.
- We tried.
It all fell apart so fast.
The infection rates
were too high.
then they just started
wiping everyone out.
It was all I could
do to keep us alive.
- You should've told me.
- You couldn't have
handled it. David.
I just. I was trying
to protect you
because. because
they're watching.
They're always watching.
Oh. if they found out
I was here. they'll...
They'll...
- It's okay.
We're not sick.
They have no reason
to us. right?
- You're bleeding.
- It's nothing.
Sam. what's wrong?
- I'm so hungry. David.
- Okay. we're together
now. so it'll be okay.
- No.
No.
No. I. I gotta go back.
- What?
- I gotta go back. David.
I can't be here.
I gotta follow the rules.
I have to go back or else...
Oh. I feel it coming.
I...
I'm sick. David.
- You said I was sick. remember?
I'm not.
- You don't believe me?
- All right.
- Yeah?
Thank you.
(Sam sobbing)
- [David] It'll be okay.
(blade slices) (Sam gasps)
It's gonna be okay.
- David?
David. no.
David.
David. no! (banging on door)
Don't leave me. David.
David.
Please don't go.
You have to listen to me.
They're watching us. David!
(soft tense music)
(David panting)
- Sam? (soft music)
It's gonna be all right.
You're not sick. You're
just confused. okay?
You need food and rest.
- David.
- [David] Yeah?
- Please. Please don't do this.
Just...
Just let me go back.
- I'll be back with food soon.
Try and get some rest.
(phone line trilling)
- [Tim] Hello. you've
reached the Beaumont family.
This is Tim-
- [Julie] And Julie.
- [Stephanie] And Stephanie.
- [Tim] leave us a message
and call you right back.
(insects buzzing) (tense music)
- Hey. it's...
Um...
I'm not infected.
I think you should come here.
I think that we'll
all be safer together.
I don't know if you have a map.
but we are at 44 degrees. five
minutes. 15 seconds by. um...
74 degrees. five
minutes. 30 seconds.
Bye. (phone thuds)
(tense music) (insects buzzing)
(David panting)
(insects buzzing)
(birds chirping)
Hey. can you see me?
- Yes. I can see
you. Can you see me?
- Yeah. I can see you.
Yeah. it's working.
- [Sam] Yay.
Hi. - Hi.
Did you get back okay?
- [Sam] Mm-hm.
Yeah.
I actually have to go.
Yeah. my uh. boss needs me.
- [David] All right.
- [Sam] Okay.
I'll see you soon.
- Yeah. okay.
- All right. I love you.
- I love you. too.
Listen to me.
I will keep him
safe and isolated.
He'll send me clean blood.
enough to suppress my symptoms
and I'll send the
rest to you via drone.
I know you need it
as much as I do.
but you will keep your
side of the bargain.
I know you're killing
anyone who's infected.
You need me.
I'm the only one he trusts.
Do we have a deal? (tense music)
(computer beeps)
Everything's going smoothly.
I've been hunting the
ones who get too close.
They come at night.
It almost seems like
they know he's here.
I'm worried he's starting
to suspect something.
He's withholding his blood.
Part of me just wants
to go to him and...
Don't worry.
He will cooperate.
Ah. it's getting worse.
I can feel it
crawling in my cells.
(Sam gasps)
Extreme vasodilation...
(Sam groans)
Inflammation.
(tense dramatic music)
I won't turn into one of them.
I need blood soon.
(tense music)
- Okay...
(computer beeping)
- Sam.
(Sam whimpering)
- [Sam] David.
Hurry. - Okay. I'm coming. Sam.
(computer beeping)
(drone clicking)
(drone buzzing)
(tense music)
Who are you?
(drone buzzing)
What the fuck do
you want from us?
(tense dramatic
music) (drone buzzing)
(drone whirring)
(gas spraying)
(David gasps)
(David choking)
(David breathing heavily)
(drone buzzing)
(tense dramatic music)
(David coughing) (David panting)
(drone buzzes overhead)
(David panting) (tense music)
(drone buzzing)
(tense dramatic music)
(arrows thuds)
(blade slices) (David grunts)
(drone buzzing)
(David thuds)
(David grunts)
(David panting)
(David groaning) (bone cracks)
Fuck.
(David panting)
(David grunting)
(birds chirping)
(David panting)
(David grunts)
Sam!
(David panting)
(David groans)
(David breathing heavily)
(David panting)
(blade slices) (David yelps)
(David groans)
(David panting)
(soft clicking)
(Sam smacking lips)
(Sam whimpering)
(egg timer ringing)
(Sam thuds) (Sam gasps)
(Sam snarls)
(Sam clicking
tongue) (Sam snarls)
(Sam screams)
(David panting)
- Sam?
Sorry.
(drone buzzes in the distance)
Sam. I can give you blood.
Things will go back to
how they were. okay?
I can give you some.
(tense music)
(Sam softly snarls)
(Sam clicks tongue)
(David panting)
(footsteps thudding)
(Sam snarls)
(Sam clicks tongue)
(Sam whimpering)
(David breathing
heavily) (Sam whimpering)
(Sam snarls)
(Sam clicks tongue)
(Sam softly snarls)
(tense music)
(Sam clicks tongue)
(Sam screams)
(Sam clicking tongue)
- Sam. Sam.
Sam. (Sam clicking tongue)
(Sam snarling softly)
(birds chirping)
(flesh squelches)
(Sam sobbing)
- David...
(Sam clicks tongue)
(David breathing heavily)
- Sam?
(birds chirping)
Sam.
(flesh sizzling) (Sam grunts)
(David panting) (flesh sizzling)
(David panting)
(soft synth music)
(drone buzzes overhead)
(drones buzzing)
(soft music)
(birds chirping)
(flesh sizzling) (soft music)
(birds chirping) (soft music)
(David breathing
heavily) (soft music)
(David grunting)
(David grunts) (body thuds)
(David panting)
(soft music)
(flesh sizzling) (David panting)
(drones buzzing overhead)
(door thuds)
(door creaks)
(man softly panting)
- Thank you. David.
(egg timer ringing)
(egg timer continues ringing)
(computer beeps)
David?
Is that you?
- My name. um. my
name is Dr. Chambers.
- Where's David?
- David left.
- Is he all right?
- Yeah.
Yeah. they found a
treatment for him.
He. uh. he left to D.C.
to be with his wife.
I'm afraid we have
some bad news. though.
The previous generation
of tests was flawed.
From what we know now. it
seems that everybody out there
who's still alive is an
asymptomatic carrier.
We believe you are. too.
But we can start
working on a treatment
for you right away.
In the shelves to your left.
you'll find
phlebotomy equipment.
tools to collect
samples of your blood.
You're safe now.
Let's get started. (tense music)
(tense dramatic
electronic music)
(tense music)
Watch Online Movies and Series for FREE
www.osdb.link/lm